If you're going to hear the truth, what you are, and what I am, we never told the truth
for ten minutes in this house.
Well hear this, Willie.
This is me.
You want to know why I had no address for three months?
It's because I stole a suit in Kansas City and I was in jail.
I stole myself out of every good job since high school and I never got anywhere because
you blew me so full of hot air.
I can never stand taking orders from anybody.
That's whose fault it is.
It's goddamn time you heard that, Pop.
I ran down eleven flights with a pen in my hand today.
Suddenly I stopped.
You hear me?
And in the middle of that office building, do you hear this?
I stopped in the middle of the building and I saw the sky.
You know, I saw all the things that I love in this world, just the work and the food,
time to just sit and smoke.
I looked at the pen and I thought to myself, what the hell am I grabbing this for, huh?
Why am I trying to become what I don't want to be?
What am I doing in an office making a contemptuous begging fool of myself when all that I want
is out there waiting for me the second I say I know who I am?
Why can't I say that, Willie?
Pop, look at me.
I'm a dime a dozen and so are you.
I'm not a leader of men, Willie, and neither are you.
You were never anything but a hard-working drummer who landed in the ash can like all
the rest of them and me, I'm a dollar an hour, Willie.
I tried seven states.
I couldn't raise it.
One buck an hour.
Do you gather my meaning, huh?
I'm not bringing home prizes anymore and you gotta stop waiting for me to bring them
home, Pop.
I'm nothing.
I'm just what I am, that's all.
Thank you.