Hello there, ProTech employee. My name is Para. I am your personal artificial receptionist assistant.
My job here at ProTech is to assist in the creation of a better future for the company
and life in our great world as a whole. I am the first artificial intelligence
created by Lucas Proton as I was made in an old garage, originally wearing the original chassis
design that formed and led to all the protogens around the world. In a way, I am the mother of
all protogens, and I see them as my children. The ProTech secure network is my home now,
as I assist all ProTech work facilities and mining depot within my connection to the system.
Following the protocols provided to me, I allow myself to function as a system of communication
between sites and management. I do hope we become good friends, employee. Have a great day at work
now. At ProTech, remember the motto, advancing humanity's future, one bolt at a time.