Log 309. Project Black Ice has finally been put into the construction phase.
Due to the nature of this project, this log is to be kept in the possession of only researchers
of the Phalanx Division and Level 6 security clearance. The project is set up to function
within the coming month. The predicted time of operation should be ready for use within a week
after functionality. The CEO of ProTech and the Board of Directory has no clue about this project
as they would never agree to the use of lethal force to fix our current issue
with our Grand Goddess. She is out of control and killing innocents,
so we are taking matters into our own hands. Last test run of Project Horizon was very successful
as we have our god in containment and secured down with Horizon.
We will continue with the test run of Project Black Ice soon.