Metallic material depot report, whelp, shit.
Currently we are missing our geothermic mining unit, otherwise named SAI,
Serviceable Auxiliary Intelligence, SAI for short.
He was last reported going into the deep mines as his directive stated for him to
do so, though we have lost all communication
with the unit since its last activation. So far we have waited for its automatic
return system to activate after the 24-hour marker, however we
believe it may have gotten stuck somewhere in the mine,
as we did record some seismic activity down in the deeper levels in the mines.
Sending order form hash 5664 RPD for our site for a replacement unit.