Hello, this is your automatic log report of your missing GTMU.
We are sorry to say, but we cannot provide a replacement unit until you provide the damaged
unit assigned to you already.
However, the log may be able to provide assistance in the matter.
Depth, 10 meters.
Depth, 50 meters.
Depth, 100 meters.
Warning, depth reaching critical levels.
Depth, 150 meters.
Warning, signal connection decreasing.
Please return immediately.
Energy levels low, energy levels low, enter.
Energy restored, please surface.
Immediately, resurface immediately.
Connection lost, rebooting.
Rebooting, host lost.
Critical damage, tracking unit, critical damage.
Connecting unit log end.
We at ProTech Industries hope this log provided assists you in your situation at hand.
Have a lovely day.